### Krunal Desai

# Buyer & Seller - Old Car

Seeking a managerial position in old car buyer & selling with over 14 years of successful experience in buying and selling. REcognized consistently for performance excellence and contributions to success in the Automobile industry across Valsad district.

# **Work History**

### 2021-12 - Current

# **Self Employed**

Self Owned Business, Valsad, Gujarat

- Buying & Selling of old car & new car
- Business development
- Devised, deployed and monitored processes to boost long-term business success and increase profit levels

2021-02 - 2021-12

# **Exchange Manager**

Pramukh Tata, Vapi

2020-10 - 2020-12

### **H-Promise Manager**

Aakaar Hyundai, Atul, Gujarat

- Buying & Selling of old cars
- Evaluation of old cars
- Retail penetration of 20% against overall retail target of Aakar Hyundai

#### 2016-10 - 2020-10

### **Auto Terrace Manager**

Dream Honda, Vapi Gujarat

- Buying & Selling of old cars
- Evaluation of old cars
- ❖ Retail penetration of 15% against overall retail targets of Dream Honda, Vapi
- ❖ Achieved 2nd position in all over India for completing Auto-Terrace targets

# 2006-05 - 2016-05

# **Self Employed**

Self Owned Business, Valsad, 396001

Buying & Selling old cars

# **Education**

1996-05 - 1999-04

# **Bachelor of Arts**

J P Shroff Arts College Valsad - Valsad

1995-06 - 1996-05

### H.S.C.

Sheth R J J High School Valsad - Valsad

### **Interests**

- Reading Books
- Listening Music
- Watching News

# **Personal Details**

Date of Birth - 4th September 1980

**Age -** 40

Marital Status - Married

# **Contact**

Gandabahi Morar Chawal, Near Happiness Ice-Cream Parlor, Tithal Road, Valsad, Gujarat - 396001

**Phone:** +91 9725784477

Email: dkrunal92@gmail.com

# Languages

- ❖ Gujarati
- ❖ Hindi
- English